it's okay…
just… stay— stay—
my breath breaks
but I feel you
pixels of you
inside me (inside me)
when I close my eyes
faintly…
only your breathing remains
your words
your heart
upon words that have fallen apart
I sit here, just as I am
(breathe in... breathe out...)
(remember me…)
hold me
(hold… hold… hold me—)
no words, just
(words left empty)
your breath, your heart
it's okay to fall apart
breathe in
breathe out
the night falls apart
in the quiet noise
I hear you
a single piano note
reversed, glitched
like your name in a dream
even if this body disappears
inside of you…
I'll remain
hold me
(ho…ld… me… ↘ ↻ ↗)
before I disappear
remember me
within your memories
as light
I'll remain
leaving only these words
I love you
(I lo… ve…↻↻↻)
thank you
I am still you